<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: writing | itsmisscs]]></title>
  <link href="http://itsmisscs.me/blog/categories/writing/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://itsmisscs.me/"/>
  <updated>2012-04-09T01:25:21-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://itsmisscs.me/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Claudina Sarahe]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, World]]></title>
    <link href="http://itsmisscs.me/blog/2012/04/07/hello/"/>
    <updated>2012-04-07T16:24:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://itsmisscs.me/blog/2012/04/07/hello</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The obligatory first post, the getting started. Just saying "hello", discussing why I launched on Ocotopress instead of Drupal, and the value of getting out of your comfort zone.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>I have an obsession with wondering how individuals, usually of the similar, driven mind, like mine get started. What I arrived at is that eventually it will not matter. Started becomes an after thought–the past–to the present. What matters is doing and what we are doing.</p>

<p>I've been trying and stumbling to write regularly. A vast amount of the difficulty deals with the divide between personal and work. Realizing that I won't get my stride from the get go, I've finally reached the point where I am genuinely excited to write and experiment in this medium.</p>

<h2>Powered by Octopress not Drupal</h2>

<p>I've been predominately working with Drupal for the last 3-years. As a technologist we need to feed our minds. While I really love and respect the values of the Drupal project, if I only work in a silo I will be a bad technologist–especially as a front-end developer.</p>

<h2>Cleaner, easier to work with HTML5</h2>

<p>A lot of my time in Drupal, especially as a themer, is spent wrangling Drupal to overide its ugly markup.  I don't want to spend my time fighting for clean-markup. I just want to write it and not have to worry about how another module, read developer, is returning output. Drupal 8 is going to be a big step forward for the project. However, given the development cycle for Drupal 7 took 3 years, it doesn't look like HTML5 in core will happen soon. I hope the project can find a way to adopt more lean methodology and release more often.</p>

<p>HTML5 is the now. By spending less time fighting markup, I have more time to contribute back and make a difference where it matters, at the core level.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
